<form>
    <field>
        <id>connection.uuid</id>
        <label>uuid</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <style>hidden_attr</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.org_uuid</id>
        <label>orignal uuid</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <style>hidden_attr</style>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.enabled</id>
        <label>enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.unique</id>
        <label>Unique</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Connection uniqueness policy to enforce.
          To avoid multiple connections from the same user, a uniqueness policy can be enforced.
        </help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.aggressive</id>
        <label>Aggressive</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>
          Enables IKEv1 Aggressive Mode instead of IKEv1 Main Mode with Identity Protection.
          Aggressive Mode is considered less secure because the ID and HASH payloads are exchanged unprotected.
          This allows a passive attacker to snoop peer identities and even worse, start dictionary attacks on the Preshared Key
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.version</id>
        <label>Version</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>
          IKE major version to use for connection. 1 uses IKEv1 aka ISAKMP, 2 uses IKEv2.
          A connection using IKEv1+IKEv2 accepts both IKEv1 and IKEv2 as a responder
          and initiates the connection actively with IKEv2
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.mobike</id>
        <label>MOBIKE</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>
          Enables MOBIKE on IKEv2 connections.
          MOBIKE is enabled by default on IKEv2 connections and allows mobility of clients and multi-homing on servers
          by migrating active IPsec tunnels.
          Usually keeping MOBIKE enabled is unproblematic, as it is not used if the peer does not indicate support for it.
          However, due to the design of MOBIKE, IKEv2 always floats to UDP port 4500 starting from the second exchange.
          Some implementations don’t like this behavior, hence it can be disabled
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.local_addrs</id>
        <label>Local addresses</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help>
          Local address[es] to use for IKE communication.
          Accepts single IPv4/IPv6 addresses, DNS names, CIDR subnets or IP address ranges.
          As an initiator, the first non-range/non-subnet is used to initiate the connection from.
          As a responder the local destination address must match at least to one of the specified addresses, subnets or ranges.
          If FQDNs are assigned, they are resolved every time a configuration lookup is done.
          If DNS resolution times out, the lookup is delayed for that time. When left empty %any is choosen as default.
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.remote_addrs</id>
        <label>Remote addresses</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help>
          Remote address[es] to use for IKE communication.
          Accepts single IPv4/IPv6 addresses, DNS names, CIDR subnets or IP address ranges.
          As an initiator, the first non-range/non-subnet is used to initiate the connection to.
          As a responder, the initiator source address must match at least to one of the specified addresses, subnets or ranges.
          If FQDNs are assigned they are resolved every time a configuration lookup is done.
          If DNS resolution times out, the lookup is delayed for that time.
          To initiate a connection, at least one specific address or DNS name must be specified.
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.encap</id>
        <label>UDP encapsulation</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>
          To enforce UDP encapsulation of ESP packets, the IKE daemon can manipulate the NAT detection payloads.
          This makes the peer believe that a NAT situation exist on the transmission path, forcing it to encapsulate ESP packets in UDP.
          Usually this is not required but it can help to work around connectivity issues with too restrictive intermediary
          firewalls that block ESP packets
        </help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>connection.description</id>
        <label>Description</label>
        <type>text</type>
    </field>
</form>
